♪ In the not too distant future
♪ Way down in Deep 13
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike
♪ Just a regular
Joe they didn't like
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin
♪ And they shot him into
space.
Let me go!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we can
find (la-la-la)
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And we'll monitor
his mind (la-la-la)
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies
begin or end (la-la-la)
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
♪ Robot Roll Call:
♪ Cambot! (Show yourself!)
♪ Gypsy! (I'm not ready!)
♪ Tom Servo! (Hello there!)
♪ Crow! (That's one "o"!)
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ and other science
facts (la-la-la)
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ for Mystery Science
Theater 3000"
(doors closing)
"I wear my
sunglasses at night."
Oh, hi everyone,
I'm Mike Nelson,
this is the Satellite
of Love and this is--
Ugh, I am so angry.
I can't remember when
I've been this angry.
Crow, what's wrong?
What happened?
I've got amnesia.
Amnesia?
Oh, can you believe it?
I of all people, Crow
T. Robot, have amnesia.
Hey, anybody know the
capital of South Dakota?
Pierre.
Oh, thanks a lot.
So Crow, about this
amnesia of yours-
Oh, its terrible,
Mike, the list of things
I can't remember is endless.
I can't remember you, I
can't remember Cambot,
I can't remember Fisk's
home run off the foul pole
in the bottom of
the 12th in game six
of the '75 World Series.
Okay, mythical beast, eight
letters, beginning with--
Minotaur.
Oh, thanks a lot.
Huh, let's see, the
last time I had amnesia,
I got somebody to hit me a
sharp blow to the head, ha.
Cleared her up right away.
Uh, would you mind, Mike?
Oh ho, I don't know,
but anything I can do
to help, I suppose.
Well, if I'm not
mistaken there should be
a large wooden mallet
under the desk.
Oh, I can't seem to, uh...
Uh, bottom shelf on
the right, way in the back
behind the lava lamp.
Oh, oh,
you're right, alright.
Well if you're ready
then, uh, here we go.
Okay.
- Oh!
- Gee.
Oh, hey, now I remember.
It wasn't amnesia I had,
it was ambrosia.
(laughs)
♪ Make a list baby
Again, harder this time.
Uh, we'll be right back.
(theme instrumental plays)
♪ Make a wish baby
♪ And love will
make it come true
Oh, come on Crow,
come on give it a rest,
or at least sing
something by Eric Carmen.
♪ All by myself,
don't wanna be...
Wait! Look! Look!
Someone's trying to contact us!
Who is it?!
What do you want?!
Who! Are! You!?
Ah, Mike, how are you?
You're probably wondering
why we're dressed
as our favorite 70's
relief pitchers;
Tug McGraw and Rollie Fingers.
Yeah, uh,
(chuckles)
Why?
That will all become
clear soon enough
my impertinent little titmouse.
Frank?
Face it Nelson,
you're ratings stink!
I mean, jeez, you draw
fewer viewers than re-runs
of the "Duck Factory".
So, to beef things
up a little bit,
we've put a little additive
in your food supply
to turn you and
your little minions
into the cast of the smash hit,
starring Lorenzo
Lamas, "Renegade".
And that's...
why we're dressed as
70's relief pitchers.
Oh, come on, there's
nothing you can put
in somebody's food
that'll turn em
into the cast of "Renegade".
(laughs)
(gasps)
(all gasp)
Keep it up, the
ratings are on the rise.
(motorcycle hums)
Yes! Baby!
Now, remember,
you're a cop who's been
wrongly accused of a crime,
and you roam the countryside,
as a bounty hunter,
looking for the
murderers of your wife.
Yes! Yes!
(mini motorcycle hums)
Oh no,
it's wearing off.
The ratings are slipping.
Ugh, did I just turn into
your wily, winnebago driving,
Native American buddy
and then back again?
Okay, this is not a problem.
Us being 70's relief pitchers
is worth at least a
full ratings point.
Uh, show em your Tug
McGraw again, Frank.
I'm Tug McGraw.
And as your
experiment this week
I've tapped into the 70's
jiggle fest, "Angel's Revenge",
starring Jim Backus
and Jack Palance,
who in lieu of pay
actually worked for scotch.
♪ On and on
Kill him, kill him.
Come on, get him.
Oh, sorry.
Whoa, whoa.
Movie sign!
♪ Movie sign
(doors open)
Crow!
♪ Dee dee dee
Stop, no more.
Well, I have yet
to be amused, ha ha.
(chuckles)
Oh the great, "Greydon Clark".
Is related to True Don Bleu?
A: Maria, the guards.
B: April, Keiko to the roof.
C: Terry, Michelle,
Elaine through the gate.
D: Explosive to the roof.
E: Down the chimney.
F: April, Keiko to the van.
G: Pick up Maria.
H: Drive the hell outta there!
Defense! Woo!
Oh no, it's not gonna work.
Why?
Well, first of all, take
off the brass knuckles.
You don't look like
you've been hurt.
Here, try this.
Lipstick?
Oh well, okay.
I have a feeling Johnny
Wad is gonna be in this.
No, not on your lips,
here on the bruise.
Oh, no!
My face!
Dear god...
Oh, that looks fine.
Mary Kay, Kay, Kay.
Good job, April.
Not quite.
Look.
Huh, Colonel Potter.
Guards on horseback.
Damn!
Language, Bernice.
That's not all, girls.
On the tower.
I don't know why, but
I think its Eric Carmen.
Let's just do
our hair and shop.
Who's not thrusting?
Well, I only saw
two guards before.
Maybe they added some after
we hit them at the beach.
Doesn't matter.
The question is,
what are we gonna do about it?
And who brought the brain?
But we've got the
plans on our side.
And we've got these!
We can still do it we can
still blow up that compound.
Maybe, but it's not gonna
be as easy as, "A,B,C".
She is the smart one.
We've voted before,
we'll vote now.
Thumbs up, we attack.
Down, we get outta here.
Hey look, it evolved last
night, it's opposable now.
Ha, it's unanimous.
I can take the
guards in the front.
No way, you're
needed on the roof.
I'm the only one
who can be spared.
If I don't make it back,
the rest of you can still
blow up this compound.
The few, the
proud, the (growls)
(laughs)
They rely on camouflage.
It's gorgeous out there,
a little too gorgeous.
Sheila Knievel.
Bounce, behave, bounce.
Oh, hi Pam.
I detect the
liver spotted hand
of Aaron Spelling
is behind this.
Stop standing that way.
Connie Stevens is
"The Professional."
Hey! You're giving
away the plot!
Great, Mitchell's here.
I hope they didn't pay a lot
for this security guy.
Dear Ranger Rick Forum,
I'm a forest ranger in a
small mid-western town...
David Mamet's Oleanna.
Ow, ooh ouch, hey,
look at the view.
Wanna have
coffee sometime?
♪ Dum, dum, dum, duuum
They're just making out.
Gene Shalit wants
his hair back.
We mourn the end
of the fight scene.
They're doing their
impression of the "Madonna".
When bad things
happen to hot people.
Oh no, I shouldn't have.
Yes, you should have!
We've got a job to do.
We have to clean the gutters.
Are we gonna do it, or not?
Yes!
To Lady Clairol.
Yes.
Apparently, someone thought
their thumbs were sexy.
If she's dead
I can't watch.
She was my favorite character.
Yes.
Don't worry.
I'll get those guys at the gate.
I'm gonna run potty
first, uh, then I'll attack.
Be Careful!
Uh, Semper Fi, marine!
(laughs)
Come on, let's go.
You got the wire cutters?
What about the
underwire cutters?
(laughs)
Kelly LeBrock's heroes.
(imitates music)
I wonder if it
aroused suspiscion
when they ordered those suits.
So these were
the "Carter Years"?
Well, I do sense
a malaise here.
Charlie was close,
I could smell his perfume.
Squanto: A Warrior's Tale.
At least they blend
in with the gravel okay.
They're attacking a
Klingon language camp.
Oh, good.
And this was Carter's
hostage solution?
I found the greatest shampoo,
it's called Body Untapped,
Herbal Essence is good,
but wait, I'll tell you
after we kill these guys.
Why, they've snuck
into the old West.
(humms "Oh Susana")
Those were big dogs.
The Green Barrettes.
Alright, you know what?
I'm just giving in and
looking at the breasts.
(laughs)
(humming "Little Drummer Boy")
For Lancome and
Isabella Rossellini!
Jose Cardenal looks on.
It's Miles O'Keeffe
with breasts.
Turns out the guy's
really a great guy.
As easy as A,B,C.
She formed a sentence.
We're up, let's go.
This movie is a shrine
for 7th grade boys.
So lucky, one of
the first DeLoreans.
Behind PTA lines.
Be right back.
Freddy Fender!
Maddie, is that the
issue you're in?
Wish I hadn't
bought a Playgirl,
aw heck,
they're nude anyway.
You know, beer and porn do
make the shift go faster.
Even for me it's
fairly pungent in here.
I've got a scathingly
brilliant idea.
Boy, I'll tell ya, we
never get anything-
(comical sound effects)
Okay, sound by
Hanna-Barbera, fine.
I think this place smuggles
black market galleries
and easy riders.
(chuckles)
Can't get enough of Super
Sugar Crisps. Doo do doo.
Hey.
Wait, don't shoot,
please don't shoot.
(chuckles)
I still like this better
than "City Slickers II".
I was walking out
in the mountains,
and well, I fell and
I scratched my cheek,
and I broke my shoe.
We fully believe you.
Is there anything
you can do to help me?
I mean is there anything
at all you can do?
Hockey moms to the rescue.
"The Mom 2000, when
you have to get them
to piano lessons safely".
The turret gun is ready!
The turd gun?
Here we go!
What do you need
one of those for?
Hang on, girls!
Vaguely Strauss, but not!
Hey, the Strauss monster's
here in his van, woo!
Not the self-styling Adorn!
Susan, do you
have any tampons?
It's the T&A Team.
It's girls, we're ruined.
Our empire is crumbling.
Flush the wax worms!
(theme instrumental plays)
This isn't as cool as
Electro Woman and Dyna Girl.
Fred Sanford!
This is the weirdest
Merchant-Ivory film.
Wow, what a pert
little grenade.
(chuckles)
It's secret redneck
world headquarters.
Yeah, they're all listening
to Charlie Daniels in there.
It's prepay after five!
Hey Vern, I can't find
your freaking legs, Vern!
Gas prices are skyrocketing.
There goes another
Pump N' Munch.
Yeah, filled with Slim Jim's
and obscene trucker tapes.
Ready? Catch!
Got it.
UPS delivers.
Didn't we just blow
up this building?
Let's go, hurry girls.
Come on!
You shouldn't wear
spike heeled boots
on a commando raid.
April, come on!
Get in here!
Put the gun in,
put the gun in!
Come on!
Oh, oh.
In to the stunt grinder.
I'm coming,
I'm coming.
Come on.
Okay.
I'll bet you're wondering
what a nice girl like
me is doing on the roof
of this building.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I'm wondering that
myself about now.
It all started a few months ago
with a street pusher
named Sticks.
He was pushing drugs to kids.
I'm a school teacher.
I carry a badge.
Some of them were my students.
Gabriel is out for justice.
This is so timely
because angels
are real, real popular.
Mmhmm.
You know, I have to say,
Jim Backus looks
good in a jumpsuit.
Hey, Mr. Haney.
I'm glad they
preserved the original
parallelogram vision format.
And Sir Laurence Olivier.
Rober Urich is "Dan Tanna."
Anytime is right
for a Beck Beer.
I'd like a drug, please.
This guy's got assistant
pro written all over him.
Not interested.
Come on,
it's a piece of metal.
Look, I'm not interested.
Why don't you go
get some money
from your rich sister
or something, huh?
I'm not a pawn shop.
I'm a human being.
Look, go get the green
stuff, then we'll deal.
Oh, my purse is a mess.
Like a little
head on your beer?
(chuckles)
You little twerp!
Why'd you hit me?!
What makes you think I did it?
You got beer on my shirt.
Is that beer?
That's blood!
I've been drinking blood?
He's a smarties dealer.
Ugh, I'm not a
very good pusher.
When I entered the
5th grade market,
I knew it'd be the
big leagues, wow.
Great, I have
to hire protection
from Mary Crest Elementary.
I'm gonna put the suit
on the aliens gave me.
(chuckles)
I will triumph
over my head injury.
Willie Aames in the
"Vince Van Patten Story".
(chuckles)
The Loneliest druggie.
Squanto in L.A.
Uh oh, the drugs
are getting washed.
They melted in the sun.
Are you sure you
know who hit you?
Yeah, look, he
snuck up behind me
and really clobbered me one.
So don't worry, I
know who the kid is,
he's been using for months.
He didn't get away with
much though, just a few--
Joints? Doobies?
Spliffs? Reefers?
Well I can't let some little
punk get away with this.
News--
And sports at 11.
has a way of
getting around fast.
Awful bad for business.
Get in.
This guys should not
be school superintendent.
Man, you are dumb.
You know that?
You are really dumb.
Ha, I've been
smoking a lot of pot.
Letting some punk
kid roll you like that.
Shame based kingpinning.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Ferrell.
It'll never happen
again, I swear!
I was dumb but I'm not now.
But uh, sorry don't
get the job done, son.
Now let's go get you a
Peanut Buster Parfait, huh?
Ooh boy, that's a
lot of earwax, ew.
Jack's down years.
Yeah.
You're not gonna
tell mom, are ya?
I'll be disappointed
if Grant Goodeve
isn't in this.
We're addicted kids,
still a million strong
and growing.
This is some hard
turf, isn't it?
Mean streets of Ojai.
There he is, Mr. Ferrell.
I told you I knew where he'd be.
Heidi Fleiss!
James at 15 miles an hour.
It's hard to
jog wearing Orlon.
If Jack could turn
the air conditioner off,
that Caddy could catch him.
Jack's not getting
paid enough to run.
The Bad News Bears
are going to lose
that game today, aren't they?
I've got Gambino ties!
SweeTarts!
Let this be a warning
to Ms. Eddington's class.
Hey, hey, dummy,
don't hurt him too bad.
He's our only customer.
Leave a roll on him so
they'll know he's a user.
Let's get the hell
out of here, come on.
Finally, it all
comes together.
Oh, kids loved Michelle
Wilson back then, remember?
Ah ha, the filthy unfunny
comedy of Buddy Hackett.
For those of you
who can't get tickets
to anything else,
stagger in drunk after
losing all your money.
(imitates horse neigh)
Well, that's not
Flip Wilson, honey...
Yes it is, it's that
Geraldine character.
♪ Always and forever you can
have this heart of mine
On second thought,
Iggy Pop, ya know?
♪ You make me wanna
shine shine shine
♪ Shine your love
♪ Shine your love on me
I lost $20,000!
(sobs)
♪ Shine your love on me
Are we getting funky?
♪ Shine shine shine shine
What am I supposed to do?
Shine, shine, shine my, shine,
♪ Shine on me
Okay.
It was a lot easier to
entertain in the 70's.
This audience would riot
if they saw KC and
the Sunshine Band.
♪ Shine shine
♪ Shine my love
Dig, dig, dig my legs.
Dig, dig, dig my midriff, yeah!
This is one of Cole
Porter's worst songs.
♪ Shine shine
♪ Shine my love
Ruth Bader Ginsberg on backup.
In the 70's, you could
take an abstract concept
like shining your love,
and just go with it.
♪ Shine shine
♪ Shine your love
Arthur Godfrey, will
you shine your love?
♪ Shine your love
Her image has
been immortalized
on pinball machines everywhere.
If shining deer is illegal,
why isn't shining your love?
You know how many people claim
they were at this concert?
Hey, how 'bout shining
my steak over here?!
♪ Shine shine
♪ Shine shine shine shine
♪ Shine your love
♪ Shine your love on me
Arthur, put a ukelele
under his tongue.
♪ Shine your love on me
♪ Why don't you shine
shine shine shine
♪ Shine shine shine shine
- How are ya?
- I'm peaking.
♪ Baby just shine
shine shine shine
♪ Shine shine shine shine
You know,
I buffed my love once,
I never shined it.
Next on Don
Kirshner's Rock Concert,
one of the greatest
influences on the disco scene
of the late 70's.
She's leaving, yay! Woo!
Now she's got one of those.
Oh, hmm.
We've never seen
such great disco.
Thank you,
thank you very much.
As most of you know,
this is my closing show
of this engagement,
and there's somebody
in the audience, I'm sure
you'd all like to meet.
The guy who cancelled me.
One of the living
legends of show business,
Mr. Arthur Godfrey.
(applause)
Thank you, you're all fired.
You have no humility,
all of you.
(belches)
You've been a
wonderful audience,
and as always Las
Vegas is the best
place in the world to entertain.
Thank you.
(doors close)
Okay, everybody.
In the spirit of the 70's,
I've come up with a
brilliant Blaxploitation film
for all of us to star in.
Crow, I don't know,
it just seems to me that
you've reworked
"Earth Vs. Soup"
and inserted jivy
character names.
Like I'm that lazy.
Now, I'm confused.
Am I Chocolate Jones
or Sugar Fly McQueen?
Uh, you're both
and you're also
reading the part of
Sweet Mama String Bean
who runs the boutique de beaute.
Okay Mike, uh,
let's see, take it from...
Afro's and Bafro's line
on the top of page five.
Okay,
Girl, don't think
on soul brothers.
I don't have any lines.
Well, but you get to
wear slinky dresses,
and hold guns and stuff.
Not this sister!
Crow, you know, I don't
know how to tell you this
but uh, I mean, look at me.
I'm really not that funky.
Mike, to me you're the
Don Cornelius of the 90's.
Well, I don't really
see it that way.
"Chocolate Jones and
the Temple of Funk"
is guaranteed boffo box office.
Smudgey the Bootblack,
which is of course, my part.
So I'll need a cane.
Oh and Mike, what size
dashiki do you wear?
Well, I'll get a large.
Now, the Cadillacs.
(theme music)
(sighs)
(knock at door)
Come in.
Where'd you go?
Mr. Godfrey, I'm
so glad you came by.
How are ya,
how are ya, how are ya?
I just came to say thank you
for that wonderful introduction.
That was very kind of you,
and I had to come
back and tell you,
you were great, wonderful.
Michelle, you're just starting.
You can have anything you want,
TV, movies, anything.
You have the makings
of a superstar,
and I've invited all the stars
that are playing Vegas this
week to come to my suite
about three o'clock
in the morning
for a little get together.
I'd love to have you come.
Can you make it?
Oh, I'd love to but
I'm doing LA tomorrow.
Get out of my dressing room.
I'd love to have
you but I understand.
Your career comes
first, of course.
You keep straight like that
and you will be a star.
Thank you Mr. G-- Arthur.
Come on over here, how
about a little co-host.
(grunts)
Thank you.
Take the wheel, Skipper.
Hey sweetheart,
I got us booked again
for The Carson Show.
Everything's going to
start happening for us.
All that work that you've
worked so hard for,
it's gonna all start paying off.
Nothing can stop us.
And with your record on the
charts and still climbing,
we're hot!
I mean, like sizzle.
Yes, but right now all
I want to do is change,
and get on that plane for home.
(phone rings)
Shining your love?
Hello.
You want me to be a greeter?
Look, don't bother her
with phone calls now.
No, I will not call
you little buddy.
Oh...
He looks a lot
like Gertrude Stein.
You better take this one.
Hello? This is
Michelle Wilson.
Oh that's sick, Mr. Godfrey!
Oh my god, not Bobby!
Is he alright?
Oh, no.
He is alright.
Three fountains in a fountain.
We're lucky.
We have a three seater bidet.
I'll pay all
expenses, everything.
He's practicing to
be on Mike Douglas.
So just take a
couple of weeks off.
Relax, that way you can go
see Bobby in the hospital
and--
I almost called you Gilligan.
Well, then you'll see,
he'll be home in no time.
Its Fran Lebowitz,
still not writing.
Excuse me Miss
Wilson, a Miss Thomas
is here to see you.
She say to tell you, she's
Bobby's schoolteacher.
And can he get her any pot?
Show her in, please.
It's the colorful domestic
who adds all the
humor to the show.
Welcome to Skipper's,
maybe you'd like
to wait in the bar.
Michelle, I'll
leave you two alone.
Now if you need anything, call.
Day or night, anything.
Pardon me.
What would you possibly need
from an Alan Hale Jr.?
I don't know.
I'm awfully sorry about
Bobby, he's a fine boy.
Nobody deserves a
beating like that.
Pauly Shore does.
He wouldn't even tell
me who beat him up.
The doctor said
he was on drugs.
How am I related
to him, again?
God, I didn't even know
he was using this stuff.
He also made an
attempt on Ford's life.
He's so young.
Bobby's lucky, he'll be okay.
Some kids aren't as lucky.
I shouldn't have left him
with just the housekeeper.
I'm talking about the men who
push poison onto young kids.
Something's gotta
be done to stop it.
very day a new drug comes along,
and these creeps
push it onto kids.
Every day?
That's good marketing.
I've got something
in here for you to see.
This is very interesting
and I've got it
in a very important place.
It's got wings.
It's in here, I
know it is, someplace.
It's really important.
I know I've got it in
here, now, just a moment.
Oh, heck!
Oh wait,
Here's a Velamints stuck
to a Kleenex, want it?
Ah, here it is.
I'm taking a big chance
showing you this.
A map of historic
Williamsburg.
I've been working on
this for over two years.
This is an area located about
75 miles east of Los Angeles.
Nearest town is
over 20 miles away.
You're booked there.
This is where
they take the stuff
that comes in from overseas,
and process it down to what
they sell on the street.
There's millions of
dollars worth of drugs
being processed
in this building.
Mmhmm.
Much of it highly
explosive chemicals.
We can destroy it in
less than a minute,
and I know the people
who can help us.
But I can't approach them,
they don't know me,
would never trust me.
But since your song
is doing so well,
and they know who you are--
Fame equals trustworthy.
Maybe we can
approach them together.
What? I wasn't listening.
You really think that
we can pull this off?
Oh yes, I'm positive!
I'm a very organized person,
and this map is perfect
in every detail.
I know we can do it.
Women can make a difference.
Ah, the director wrote
that so he could get laid.
(gun shots)
Fantastic, cut.
Clean up the corpse,
let's move on.
Barry Knight's first feature.
(chuckles)
You alright?
Sure, no sweat, it was a snap.
Did you get it, I hope?
Yeah, I think so.
How'd it look?
Terrific.
Should we have filmed it?
That's good, you can go now.
Let's get a real
actor in here please.
Uh, that'll blow
the budget sir.
Come on Rick, hurry up
with the actor, would ya?
Jesus, would you
please take your mark?
Come on, could
we get an actor?
Jeez.
Her name's Terri Grant,
she's the best stunt driver
in Hollywood.
And she's deaf.
She can drive and
modify a vehicle better
than anyone else in this town.
She'll help us, her brother
overdosed five years ago.
She's black you know.
Oh, um, Miss Grant!
That was a fantastic
stunt, are you okay?
Oh sure, thanks.
We need a real stunt sign!
Nothing to it if you
know what you're doing.
Hey, you're Michelle
Wilson, aren't you?
You're terrible.
God, I just love your voice.
Are you working on this movie?
No, but we've got something
to talk to you about,
It's about the pencil test.
and it's not making movies.
So come on in, we'll talk.
Do you have a stunt
bra for my friend?
Ya!
That's Keiko Yumaro,
here from Vietnam
a little over two years,
and knows what problems
kids can get into.
She teaches karate and
dance for these kids
in the morning.
She'll help.
She's the Asian
one in our group.
Ya!
You killed my
brother last week
Ya, ya!
Can we go?
Ya, ya, ya!
A very special,
All-American girl.
La Choy makes Chinese food.
Get her!
Rip her apart!
Kill her!
(kids cheer)
Darn it!
Now I know it's in
here somewhere.
I just know it, I
put it here myself.
Oh,
Oh, Popeye.
Here it is, oh good.
Okay, are you ready?
Do you think you could climb
to the roof of that building
and drop explosives
down the chimney?
Are you kidding?
If it keep one kid
from getting hurt,
I'll climb up to the
top of the city hall
and dump that bomb down.
Yes or no?
Hey, you know, that really
sounds great but, uh,
we're talking about a
well-armed place here.
Can you do this job or not?
Well, how many
guards are there?
Just two.
See, just two at the gate.
I don't know.
There must be more guards
inside those buildings.
It would sure help to
keep those guards' attention
away from the roof
of that building.
I've got an idea.
What a great idea,
Miss Max Fly.
Her name's Maria.
She could keep
the guards' attention
away from the roof
of the building.
She'll help us.
She's an ex-junkie.
She's gone to prison a
little over six months.
You've all probably seen
her pictures in a magazine.
In Purge World.
She's a top model.
That's why they shoot
her in mall parking lots.
You're so beautiful.
She's bouncing on
Alan Hale's stomach.
Move to your left,
just a little bit.
Great, great!
Lemme see, shake your head out,
shake your head.
Hi, teach!
Oh, hello Trish.
How are you today?
No school, I'm cool.
Hey teach, is that
Michelle Wilson?
She sucks.
Uh, yes it is, excuse us.
She rejected me, I'm
gonna go use drugs.
We will, like, bury you.
I wonder where Maria is.
Singing with the Von Trapp's.
Terri, are you sure
we can trust her?
I'm positive, look, you
girls gotta learn how-
Hi, everybody.
I trust her.
(chuckles)
See?
This is Elaine Brenner,
she's a friend of mine.
She helped me when I needed her,
and boy, we could
sure use her help now.
She's flat, but I
think we can trust her.
Maria told me about your plan.
I think it might be successful.
I interrupted my
perm to come here.
It'd be worth the attempt.
I don't think we
really need your help.
Let's listen to her, Terri.
Maria told me about this.
I've been guarding
the one potato two
for about a week now.
You're April, right?
What's your plan?
Who's your daddy?
We're gonna drop a
bomb down the chimney
of that building.
And then drugs will be gone.
That's a nice idea,
but it's not a plan.
I mis-emphasize words.
Where's this compound located?
When the time comes, I'll
show you all where it is.
If that's the way you
want it, that's alright.
Now let's assume that these--
Are baked beans.
are the three buildings.
Watch the lady,
watch the lady.
This is our target,
Don't spill my fish balls.
and this is the main gate.
Okay.
Maria gets the
guard's attention, here.
You, shine your love.
April and Keiko,
cut through the wire and get
to the roof of this building.
Who here speaks German?
Michelle, Terri and myself--
Shave our heads
and get to Brussels.
Bust through the main gate.
We'll need a heavy
duty van or a truck
to hit that gate.
That's no problem,
I'll buy us anything we need.
And I can fix up a
van so it'll blast
through any gate and nobody
will be able to stop us.
Alright, I think it's great!
Kill her.
Trish, what are
you doing here?!
Well, I heard you ask
Maria for help and--
This is no place for a kid.
I can help.
And it's extra credit.
Besides, I know what you
guys are planning to do and--
Are you trying
to blackmail us?
No, but I can
help around here.
ook, look, I'll put things away,
and I can help with the meals.
(laughs)
Suddenly I'm
thirsty for a Seven.
So what do you think?
Not enough deep shag.
I don't know.
This happened on
Designing Women once.
What do you think, Terri?
Hey, don't worry.
When I get through
with this thing,
it'll be fantastic.
Right on, Willona.
Well, howdy girls, shall
I gasoline her up for ya?
Well, mercy mercy
says Mrs. Percy.
You girls are as pretty as
a creek full of catfish.
Oh, it's that old
bastard from the TV.
You need this van.
I can make you a deal as sure
as a goose goes barefooted.
Now all you gotta do is
put a little down payment,
and the paltry sum of
$12,673.88,
it's all yours.
Just as it stands.
Well, maybe we could
make a deal about the $73.
Hey, you're the pick of the
litter, did you know that?
Then how about the 88 cents?
Ow, my artificial hip!
Hey, hold it there.
Hi-Ya!
You girls sure
do cover a vehicle.
You jump around,
it's like a rooster
going through a henhouse.
Never mind about the
trading stamp's tax,
just mail the title to
the address on the check.
Alright, it's ours.
Let's go, girls.
The check.
Wait, I've got more
barnyard analogies.
Hold it there, the check!
Uh, wait, girls!
I have to circle
your phone number
before you can leave.
Hey, it has to be verified!
For more information on
the Patt Buttrum Fan Club.
This is made out
to Gabby Hayes.
They'll recall the
van back to the factory
in a few weeks anyways.
Olympia Dukakis,
ladies and gentlemen.
(laughter)
(theme music)
Look at this.
They can get,
"All My Children".
(laughing)
It's the Charlene
Tilton channel.
What's the cross for?
A little surprise for
anybody following us.
You see that bazooka?
I like this.
Sometime's a bazooka
is just a bazooka.
This is really nice.
Just push that button,
and whoever was following us,
boom!
Ain't no more.
Plus it's got
neat pop holders.
This is really neat.
I mean, really!
Uh oh, you forgot
the battering ram.
We've gotta bust through the
main gate of the compound.
It's just a big
hotel ice maker.
It's all built in,
3 or 4 inches steel.
She'll take any
gate and a lot more.
We've gotta do one more
thing before we destroy
that processing compound.
Everybody go potty.
Oh no, what did I forget?
We've gotta lay our hands
on some heavy ammunition
to arm this baby.
There's a bunch of
right-wing military fanatics
that headquarter out
in Ventura County.
They've got an organization
called "The American Right".
Headed by Newt Gingrich.
They've got an arsenal there.
They're prepared to
start World War Three.
If we're gonna
steal their guns,
we'd better check it out first.
Like I always tell my students,
"Preparation is
the key to an A+"
I'll go down and snoop
around as a potential member.
Eww!
That's not good Elaine,
they might recognize a cop.
Well, how about me?
I could tell them,
I wish to make a big donation
from my poor deceased
husband's estate.
(sighs)
I'll shake my bod a little.
Then we'll get all the
ammunition we need.
Okay, and to make this work,
I'll go as your chauffeur.
Just in case
there's any trouble.
Trouble?
But we're pretty.
Do you think there
might be some trouble?
Oh no, you can handle it.
Just put the mason brass
knuckles in your purse.
Can't they just
buy some ammunition?
Well, I never go
anywhere without them.
That's mousse.
And we'll be close
by, just in case.
And I can climb through
a window or something.
Not that it'll help.
Or you can stand by
the phone in the garage,
in case of any emergency.
(laughing)
I never get to
do any of this stuff.
Wa-ya-hi-ya!
(chuckles)
Hey, it's Glenn
Russell's house.
You and your date
will be chauffeured
to exotic Centerville,
Minnesota.
Here comes the Prime
Minister of Greece.
She must be engaged
to Sean Penn.
(laughs)
Look at that, Stanley.
She's getting more
and more Tina Louise-y.
Wheezy.
Mrs. Hildago
Campbell, of Houston.
You were expected,
Mrs. Campbell.
Step right this way.
We're going to prom.
Thank you.
She's an arachnid.
Blegh.
Hired help must wait outside.
If you don't mind, I'll
go with Mrs. Campbell.
You better step aside.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
I've given fair warning.
Now now, dear,
you'll do as you're told.
No more, no less.
Ah yes, yes, yes, yes,
Uh, welcome, welcome,
Ms. Campbell.
Delighted to make
your acquaintance.
I am commander Lindsey March.
Commander of the American Right.
Yes, the pleasure will
be all mine, I'm sure.
Jim Backus is
John Phillips Sousa.
Oh, you lovely ladies
and your lovely rings.
How many of those are
load bearing straps?
Oh, there's seems to be some
problem about my chauffeur.
Well we have very tight
security here, if you know it.
We must all follow
the same rules.
Do you understand?
Well, yes I do and
I am quite pleased.
Perhaps I should
inspect your security?
I mean, before I'm to
make any big donation.
Well, my late husband always
taught me to be very cautious.
Very wise, very wise
of your late husband.
How did he come
to his sorry end?
He got swine flu.
Oh, in the saddle I'm afraid.
Oh, what a way to
go, in the saddle?
Yes he was, um,
thrown from his favorite horse.
Oh how tragic,
would you care to--
Finish my sentence.
With my chauffeur?
With your chauffeur?
Well no, perhaps we better make
a tour of the grounds first.
Would you please, Sergeant!
This was Jim Backus'
first film after he died.
I didn't know that.
Clean up this
mess immediately.
Yes sir, right away sir!
Insubordination.
These survivalists couldn't
survive a grape embargo.
I want to take you on
the tour of the facilities
since you're here.
That's going to be
the parade ground
and the barracks
are way past there.
Then we have livestock.
I intend this
entire establishment
to be self-sustaining.
I was hoping to
never see Jim Backus
in thigh high boots.
And here's where we grow dirt.
Its Knight Rider, for moms!
So Jim Backus runs
a trout hatchery?
(laughs)
And we're thinking of starting
a fascist petting zoo!
(chuckles)
If only poor Jim
had gotten residuals
from Gilligan's Island.
Yup.
And Mrs. Campbell,
you will find that your very
generous contributions
will put to very good use.
Everything, of course,
is legal
and all our properties
are sacrosanct
under the law.
Don't you know.
Excellent.
And you have no fear of
criminal elements attempting
to steal your supplies?
Oh, none whatsoever, my
men are more than equal
to the task,
as you can see.
This scene was
totally improvised.
(chuckles)
The Hudson brothers were
funnier than these guys.
Where do you want me to
put this, commander, sir?
Just put it down,
will you Sergeant?
(crashes)
John Irving as Adolph
Hitler in "The Bay".
Perhaps you'd come in here
and I could offer you a drink?
Oh, no thank you,
Commander March,
but I am running a little late.
We'll have to conclude
our business another time.
Come on, Terri.
I hope the problem with
your servant hasn't uh--
Tell you what,
let's you and me
shake and make up.
Only out of respect
for your beautiful
and generous employer.
(knuckles cracking)
You know, who couldn't
do that to Jim Backus?
Terri, why don't you stop?
We'll come back later.
You have my promise.
You know, now I
appreciate the quiet dignity
of Pat Buttram's performance.
Help me up, will you?!
Respect the uniform!
I'm just gonna look away
until the funny part is over.
Oh, I understand it took
hours to get this shot.
(laughing)
(theme music)
Uh, let's see, do
you have any fives?
Fives, fives,
uh, nope.
No fives.
Hey you guys, check it out.
Ayyyy!
Uh, huh?
Uh, hold that thought, Mike.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Hey.
Ayyy.
Fire in the hole!
(explosion)
So, any jacks?
Uh, no,
go fish.
(alarm sounds)
Oh, movie sign.
(doors open)
Sorry we had to
destroy you, Mike.
You understand.
I do.
You know, I'm starting to root
for the drug dealers
in this movie.
"Sto", "Sto" or I'll "shoo".
Get them!
Look everyone,
I made a potty.
Full speed, full speed ahead!
I'll be there with you,
your fearless leader.
Circus of the B-movie stars.
I'm coming, you hear me?
Never fear, men, never fear,
the commander is here!
Who's got the key?
You've got the key!
I've got the key?
Uh, here, hold this.
I've got the key, there you are.
I'd rather spend a weekend
in Robert Bork's underpants,
than watch more of this.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Boy, when Jim Backus turns
on the funny meter, huh?
Unlock the gate!
Could those brightly
lit tight white jumpsuits
deeply decolletaged women
have anything to do with this?
(yelling)
Still it's all
going much smoother
than the Bay of Pigs operation.
Suddenly, Allan
Hale felt much better
about his performance.
After them, after
them, get the guns!
So Jim Backus is the
god of wine, right?
I believe this
Tom Clancy novel
really loses something
in the film version.
Lovey!
Women, and they're
fully boobed.
Hold it, gentlemen.
Get over there.
In the name of
Natalie Schafer,
you're all under arrest.
The Apollo astronauts.
Wait a minute, that
turkey's all mine.
Miss Jane Pittman
in striking distance.
Ow!
(crash)
Oh, an Owen Thompson home.
(laughing)
Jimbo, I'll be a
man for you, Jimbo.
And Jim Backus gracefully
closes his career.
(gun fires)
The Five Mrs.
Buchanan's on a rampage.
(gun fires)
My Snapple!
I'm the NRA and it's fun!
The Marines have landed!
And it didn't take
us any four months
of police officer
training either.
Yeah, but it didn't take
you three months of learning
how to march in a straight line.
Eh, its hard to
follow Jim Backus.
Elaine, can I please?
Please, lemme try, come on!
Well, yeah,
Yeah!
Please?
Okay, we'll give
you a chance to act.
This is the same gun I used
to shoot my Phy Ed. teacher.
Can I fire now?
Fox Force Five.
Ready. Aim.
Pull.
Fire!
(gun fires)
Why does it jump if I-
Be careful!
You ruined my pedicure.
My period.
I'd better go
after her, poor kid.
No Michelle, I'll do it.
I'll bring her back here and
really teach her how
to fire this thing.
Even if it kills me.
God, she's so thin.
I hate her.
Well, I think we're ready to
hit the processing compound.
Van's ready, so am I.
Uh, I'm afraid we
may be a little late.
There's word going
around the school
that the shipment's about
to hit the street any day.
Why didn't you say something?!
That was the whole point!
We should hit it before
it gets on the street.
If we don't stop
that shipment,
that poison will
be hooking kids.
Let's stop it then.
Alright, I agree, but how?
We don't even know where
the shipment's coming in.
And we need our hot rollers.
I know a guy that can tell us.
Marjoe Gortner?
Go ahead on seven,
tight pants.
(snickers)
Well, the oil embargo
is going to affect
his shirt supply.
Geeze, you need orangutan arms
to reach the gas cap.
(dramatic music)
Hi, do you know where
we can score some gas?
Hey!
Sticks, baby!
Where you been?
Where'd you get this machine?
Hey Cheech, man!
Tell you what, you outta
come inside and have a look.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What you got in there?
Well, why don't
you come in and see?
Hi, Stick.
Hey, what you got in there?
She beat me up
in her Chevy van,
and that's alright with me.
Oh, he's having a baby.
What a lovely way for him
to say how much he loves me.
(chuckles)
Before we start
between his legs,
let's ask him one more time.
Tell us the exact
location of the next pickup,
pusher man.
Cookie man!
What pickup?
I don't know anything
about a pickup.
Scum like you have
been poisoning kids.
Come on, I never
poisoned anyone,
just put me down,
come on girls.
Maybe you don't
think we're serious.
Right here, Keiko.
No, come on!
These are my Chess King pants!
This is the guy
that hooked me,
so don't be too careful.
This is a tough fourth step.
Come on baby, you
know I always liked you.
No, no!
It's Dworkin Fest 78'
These kids just love
genital mutilation.
Okay, okay, I'll tell you,
just let me down, alright?
Just let me down!
Alright, pusher man.
When? Where? And how?
Come on,
I can't even think straight.
Just let me down on
my feet I'll tell ya!
Come on!
Need a little more persuasion.
It's a wonton,
unauthorized bris.
No come on, you win!
They're revoking
his member-ship.
(swords hit)
Ooh!
Wow!
(gasp)
Meanwhile, on the
beaches of Scotland.
Yay.
Whoopee.
Professional beach
volleyball wasn't that good
in the early days.
Maybe Sticks lied to us.
I don't see
anything out there.
Who could see
anything in this fog?
Darn it.
Well, he said
this was the place.
With the helpful hardware man.
Where the buoys are.
Oh please.
That'd be a pretty
good trick, Billy.
Since your line is tied
to a buoy out there
in the middle of the ocean.
Don't rob me of my joy, Joe.
Idiot.
Hey Joe, look,
we've got company.
Can't those chicks read?
We put a sign up.
Private beach.
Hey, they ain't half bad.
Let 'em stay, what can it hurt?
Come on.
You wanna tell the boss that?
Springsteen?
Oh yeah, I see what you mean.
Billy, go get rid of them!
I don't care how you do it,
but get rid of them, understand?
I'll keep looking for the drop.
Here, hold this ,will ya?
Will you put that
down? Right now!
Ooh, he's got
crotchless waders on.
Looks like this could be fun.
Them chicks might
just get lucky.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Alright!
I have to go shower now.
I understand.
I just can't wait
for the outtakes
at the end of the movie.
You know what
this scene needs?
Eddie Deezen.
Ah ha!
Hey, yeah!
Should we open the chicken?
What do you think?
Um, I don't.
Look, someone's coming.
Uh, pardon me ladies,
but uh, see this sign?
Private beach.
It says right here.
"P-r-i",
Well you got your "pri",
"v-a-t-e",
there you got your "vate".
Finally, someone Jim
Varney can feel superior to.
Well, okay, so they
spelled it wrong,
but the point is, this
is a private beach,
and you're gonna have
to get your privates
outta here.
Show 'em the wiener.
We're sorry, we just
want to be by ourselves
and get some sun.
Sun?
There ain't no sun
in this weather.
Well, we wanna get some fog.
Yeah.
Would you like to
get some with us?
What do you think about that?
You play basketball?
Oh, this is offending
one-celled animals.
I'm sorry girls, but
they're gonna have to leave.
I mean, they're all
gonna have to leave.
Sandy Hackett,
ladies and gentlemen.
You're right, there's no sun.
So why don't you bring
your friend over here,
and we'll all have
some fun in the fog.
We'll provide you with sex,
which is something
that men like.
I just can't right now.
Aw, come on.
Look this is a private
beach and you're really--
My ass itches.
I'm sorry.
Fishing can't be that
much fun now, can it?
Wait Miss, you
don't understand,
Just shut up and
take your clothes off.
This doesn't do it for me
like that similar scene
in "The Violent Years".
Yeah, director
doesn't have Ed Wood's
passion for this kinda material.
You really want me
bad, don't ya, baby?
Hey that's cool,
if you girls can't
leave without me--
(gagging)
Oh, Robert Reich is sailing.
Nice day!
Don't do that!
I bet the phrase
"Where's my cocaine"
was heard a lot on this film.
Looks like your friend
caught more than fish!
Oh, that ignorant...
But no use him
having all the fun.
We've got plenty to share.
We have additional
sex for you also.
Focus on the buoy,
just focus on the buoy.
(groaning)
I hope those are stunt tongues.
They're eating his brain!
Ohuh, this is
your brain on sex,
any questions?
Well.
Why not, I can't see a
thing out of these anyways.
But only for a
few minutes, okay?
Sure, that's long enough.
Oh, he's inflated his chest
to impress the females.
Gonna get medieval on his ass.
You really know
how to follow orders,
don't you, Billy?
(muffled protests)
What did you say?
Oil can, oil can!
Oh.
All right.
Thought you'd keep all
this to yourself, huh?
(muffled speech)
Now girls, I don't
have a lot of time.
Get your clothes off.
All right, well,
I have to warn you
I have an elaborate
network of trestles.
Hey, what is this?
Just drop your pants, stud.
And start talking.
Now what about that shipment?
Shipment of pants?
I don't know any
shipment of pants.
Does this mean the date's off?
(imitates comedic bassline)
Ah, smugglers
alerted their contacts
by wearing really dumb hats.
I still like this better
than the Blue Lagoon.
Send...
acting coach.
C and H, pure cane sugar
from Hawaii.
It's the Mario
Hemingway boatlift.
They're gonna do it!
Oh good, oh good.
Get up on the rock!
The survivors of
the Achille Dora
have made it around the buoy,
but here come the
survivors of the Titanic
looking very good coming on.
They wanted Bob
Denver for this role.
Get on the rock!
Okay, oh good.
Pull!
I am, I'm pulling,
I'm pulling!
Harder!
Okay, okay.
It took 20 guys
to drop that off?
(laughter)
I'm pulling, I'm pulling!
What kind of lure do you use
to catch cocaine?
A spoon?
Meanwhile, Richard
Nixon's wasting millions
on the Glomar Explorer.
I'm pulling, I'm
pulling, wait, wait.
The Kamoa that fell
from grace with the sea.
We got it, we got it!
This could be a
light tackle record!
We got it, we got it.
It's stuck, hold on.
Oh no.
We got it, we got it!
Okay, okay.
My hair, damnit, Brooke!
Quick, pretend
you're Sean Phillips!
(groaning)
It's that fella that did 'em!
Hurry, hurry!
Jane Campion's
"The Piano Stool".
(murmuring)
Get out of here!
Okay, okay, be careful.
Come on, quick!
As fast as you can!
Okay, okay!
Come on, move!
♪ Yummy yummy, a
digga-digga boom boom
♪ Digga-digga flavor oceans
Hurry!
They're getting close!
Did they row all
the way from Columbia
to drop off the drugs?
This is straight out of
the Bradys in Hawaii.
The Mommies, an
action-packed adventure.
D-cup day.
I'm sure Gidget's
tied up in this somehow.
At least the weather
cleared up instantly for them.
(laughter)
Okay, sister, drop it!
I'm so sure.
I got the merchandise.
(screaming)
Mrs. Paul and Long John Silver
in a battle to the death.
(grunting)
Thank you, Nair,
for making this fight possible.
More Jackie O
than Jackie Chan.
Oh my back!
Oh woopsie daisy,
are you okay?
Why it's Max Padkin,
the clown prince of baseball.
Hey that's my womb!
Try this nightie on.
(grunting)
Scenes cut from
The Longest Day.
Right now Bennie Hill
is smiling down from heaven.
(laughing)
I wonder what's in
those boats over there.
I don't know, let's go.
By going, we'll find
out what's in them!
(laughter)
These would look so
cute in the bathroom!
(oohing)
They are gonna get so high.
In response to
the energy crisis,
Cadillac produces
this new subcompact.
(singing)
I'm Lyle Waggoner,
may I help you?
Somebody's dad is in there.
Is that a Sears 12-piece suit,
or is it from the Johnny
Carson collection?
Welcome back to
jail, Mr. Goddy.
You know you're old
when you got curb feelers
in your car.
Police discovered eight
men bound and gagged
at the beach today.
Evidence of narcotics
was discovered
and the men are being held--
You're listening
to K-Plot.
(dog barking)
Dad, Jethro's down
in the sea men pound.
They're listening to
one of those nature tapes.
Peter Lawford's got
Christie McNickel hair.
Release Baby.
(snaps fingers)
Hey Mike, I bet that's you
in high school, huh?
(laughs)
You're not far off, my friend.
The doberman gang
in a one-man show.
(whispering)
It's Englebert Humperdinck.
He's gonna sing him to
sleep after the lovin'.
I crap bigger than you.
Maybe these are
his Kibbles and Bits.
(snaps fingers)
He's telling me
to kill my parents.
You think Peter has
any idea where he is?
Hey, come on.
You know I'm lactose intolerant.
(snaps fingers)
Ah, maybe one, then
the Stairmaster.
(laughs)
Can I have
another Buttermints?
Control, Mike.
It's all control.
And we're all beasts
in the same jungle.
Sometimes we
eat our own vomit.
We lose control, we're lost.
Uh-huh.
And incontinent.
See, Baby here,
he loves me.
But if I lost control
of him for one instant,
he'd tear my throat out.
But he's great with kids.
Do you understand me?
I'll take care of things,
just like we agreed,
but I can't conrol
these junkie gangs.
Mike, control is
the key of life.
We have to control everything,
or we will be controlled.
Control (mutters)
Now if you can't do the job--
Oh come on now,
you know I can do it.
I've been contolling
things for years.
We both made a lot of money.
Now try to clean this mess up.
Hey, it's your dog.
I'd hate to have
to do it myself.
Can you borrow me
some swim trunks?
Yeah.
I can't believe I drove
all the way up here for this.
If you're going to
wake me up this early,
you got to expect me to drink.
(theme music)
Hey, hey, hey,
what are you doing?
Now they're gonna force him
to fix their tranny.
I told you everything
you wanted to know!
I can't tell you
any more, I swear!
It's all I know.
I swear I don't know any more!
I told you all of it!
Please, you can't kill me!
Maybe we should
give him a chance.
Yes, yes!
That was incredible.
Maybe Keiko's right.
Maybe we should give
him another chance.
Okay, we'll vote on it.
Everybody take a full
and an empty cartridge.
I like the thumb voting.
Full round means death.
Empty cartridge
means second chance.
And sha la la la
means I love you.
Kind of an NRA
voting procedure.
Chuck Heston kind of voting.
You too, Trish.
I want to go to the mall.
Give us Jim Backus!
Pygmalion.
Six empty, one full.
Majority rules.
It's a bad day at Tires Plus.
Okay, Sticks, you've been
missing for over two days now.
And your friends are bound
to figure you had a part
in hitting that
shipment at the beach.
And don't go turning
on any more kids
to anything anywhere.
'Cause we'll find out,
and we'll come after you
no matter where you are.
I swear, I'm never
pushing stuff again.
Can I have my weiner back?
All right.
I'm tired of looking at him.
Let's get him out of here.
This is a full-service
station, huh?
Okay, clean him up
and tell the owner he's ready.
Yeah, ride!
Riding like the dude when
you drive to your dreams.
(muttering)
Mom! Mom!
A bunch of girls took my
drugs and snagged on me!
How will I make it on my own?
(laughs)
The Cronas Quartet
live on this block
with Bartok, apparently.
I was lucky to get a space.
(intense music)
Draw.
I'm leaving you.
I just want to talk to you!
I've arranged
counselling for you
at the members' center!
I'm William Katt
for Samsonite.
H-I-S by Chick.
It's locked!
Oh, he should have learned
his own apartment
complex better.
(panting)
Oh my God, my
heart's gonna explode.
Damn you, gated communities!
Well, I'll ask
the fellow in here
if he knows where that guy went.
(grunts)
You are the most
childish drug kingpin
I've ever hired.
Hey, your bag is too big
to fit in the
overhead compartment,
I'll have to ask
you to check it.
We tout tradition.
We are like drugdealer
on the roof!
Underalls for men.
Ding, ding.
My suit still looks great.
This was filmed on
location, you know.
We continue now with
international hide-and-seek!
Look, just take A
Watchtower and read it.
Did you borrow my good
tie, the Countess Mara?
Look.
Just take is easy.
All I want to do is talk to you.
Listen, get out of my way!
I have to crouch
by that other spot.
Get out of my way!
Don't try it, kid.
Listen, come on!
(intense music)
Hey, wait!
(yells)
Oh oh!
Oh the whole building just
lost The Price is Right.
Help! Help me!
Help me up!
Please help me!
Jeez, he might
fall a whole 12 feet.
All right, I'll help you.
First you gotta help me.
You got me into a lot of
trouble with the big boss.
Tell me where you've
been the last few days
and who hit one
of our shipments.
Help, help me up!
Pull me up!
No, no, tell me right now.
What?
Just please, pull me up!
Tell me!
Boy, he's had to
answer a lot of questions
under duress lately
Please, help me!
Help!
(yells)
He should die for
those pants alone.
(crashes)
Ooh, sorry ma'am.
Oh, that's okay.
Wonder if I could
sunbathe nude up here.
(laughter)
So now you know what kind of
creeps we're dealing
with and why
a nice schoolteacher
like me is trying
to blow up the building.
That was a long flashback.
(laughter)
Oh, okay, wait, wait.
Wait!
Correct-All made
this jump possible.
(cheering)
So they just destroyed
all the drugs in the world?
Huh.
Are we hot or is it just us?
We killed lots of
people (mock laughs)
Richard Farnsworth
is out for justice.
(explosion)
My Charlie Daniels
t-shirt is in there!
That was some hot chili, whew!
So much for the historic
registration designation.
Woo-wee.
(laughter)
Wait a minute,
this is a lot like
Charlie's Angels!
Hey!
Yeah!
Oh gee, I thought I dropped
a bomb in there, but wow.
Thank you, Metamucil.
(excitedly chattering)
Did you see the
Jen was dressed
duing the raid?
I mean, really?
Hi, Carrie!
The war on drugs
was never sexier.
Girls, we've got company.
Get out the good linen.
They're gonna get
our little surprise.
No, I just speed-dialed
my manicurist.
(blast)
Oh jeez, it was just
the Johnson family
going to mass.
Oh, now how will the kids
get to band practice?
(singing)
(murmurs)
All right, I'm
gettin' out of here.
I'm digesting
my food right now!
Hal Needen's golddiggers
are off to another adventure.
(laughter)
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the reason this movie was made.
Did you guys see
this girl on her bike?
That was neat.
You weren't so
bad yourself, girl.
All of us were great!
Hey, where's April?
In Paris.
I thought beating
the druglords
would be more
fulflling than this.
(whistling)
Yeah.
Why not?
Acting lessons
are a good idea.
We're a team,
a darn good team.
We did it once,
we can do it again!
(mechanical whirring)
♪ Some say love
Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike!
Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike!
Steve!
Mike!
What's happening?
What's going on?
(screaming)
What the-
Cambot,
get me rocket number nine!
It's Aaron Spelling's house.
Shh, don't disturb it,
it might charge.
Majestic, yet graceful.
Wow, this could take a while.
I feel so insignificant.
We'll be right back.
(theme music)
(dramatic music)
Wow.
Big.
Good morning.
I got a message you
wanted to see me.
Oh my God, you're nude.
Ah, that's a
pic-ah-so, isn't it?
Hey, that's, uh,
that's beautiful.
It's got a
wonderful other-ness.
It's like Picasso
with the funny eye,
and that rose, that's, uh...
You're gonna kill
me, aren't you?
I guess you're waiting
to hear that I got
the broads that hit us, huh?
Got the bras that fit us?
Our processing plant
completely destroyed?
Better than 10 million
dollars worth of good product
down the tube.
Sinatra won't talk to me.
Very frustrating, Mr. Farrell.
Very frustrating.
Very, very frustrating.
I talked to you
before about control.
Control, control.
What plans do you have to
control this situation now?
Well, look, actually I was
on the way out to the compound,
I thought that maybe I could
find some evidence, you know?
About who, you know...
They cut the wires with these.
Ah, Snap-On, yes.
Got a lifetime
guarantee, you know,
a very good tool this is.
I can have these checked
out for fingerprints.
You're late again.
Some dumb school teacher.
Oh, now our educational system
isn't perfect, but...
Hey, she was my
teacher, she's hard.
At least Jack
got in a good one
before he left.
It's not my fault JFK stayed
at Crosby's house.
She got that at the fair.
Okay, don't forget to study
for the test tomorrow.
What test?
Oh, it's not gonna be hard.
It's about killing drug lords.
Teacher's pet.
I want to be teacher's pet.
You'll pass if you're lucky.
Oh yeah, maybe.
Well, bye teach.
Be careful.
Don't tell anybody about
the people we killed.
(singing)
I think it would be
fun to waste a pusher.
Miss?
May I speak to you
for a moment, please?
It's about my report card.
Yes?
What can I do for you?
What's this incomplete crap?
You're Miss Thomas, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
I would like to talk to
you about my nephew, he's...
Jonesin' real bad.
Got a little trouble.
You're his teacher,
I understand.
Oh sure, I have a few moments.
What's his name?
You broads really think that
you can get away with this, huh?
Well that's a weird name.
Come on!
Hey, no fair fake-hitting me.
Damn, I forgot
you were a commando.
You sure it's Miss
Thomas's picture?
That's right, I saw it.
Hey, don't you
want to make out?
Hm.
You are now on six
days' detention, mister.
Oh do, do, oh, you got a saw?
Trish, I'm so
glad you came back.
Come over here and help me.
No, no, get to a
phone and call the girls,
tell them I'm bringing
him in for a confession
so we can find out who
the real bigshot is.
Just like we did Sticks.
This time I'm gonna
use that big sword.
Hurry and go before
we're discovered,
and I'll meet you
back at headquarters.
It's so cool that
we got a headquarters.
(singing)
Oh, Dick Turden's ugly.
Well yeah, she's
turning in the car now
and she's bringing him in.
Well, well, we'll
stay there and, and,
oh no.
Her left front tire is low!
He's got her!
He's got April!
This looks like a
job for Girl Woman.
Trish, Trish, wait!
The phone comitted suicide.
Trish, wait a minute!
This world is awfully big.
Girl, this time I'm on my own.
With each glance and
every little movement
I know it.
(dramatic music)
Mrs. Breaking Away.
I'm on a cycling
tour of North Cornwall.
Wait here, Black Beauty.
Oh, she's on a date.
(gasping)
(singing)
Hey mister, you're dragging
your high school girl!
He's got a dent.
Good thing she
has suction cups
on her fingers.
This all works fine 'til they
go to the car wash.
Oh, I think she
loves me so what am I
(yawns)
(imitating dramatic music)
Did I lock my bike?
Oh, help.
I really think taking
the 105 would be faster.
If he drops her on
that part of the road
it's a $500 fine.
Do you think that's
a stunt person?
No, it's Marnie Nixon.
Oh shoot, I'll have to roll
the rest of the way.
You see, this is
why getting a bus pass
is a good idea.
Oh, my bone is
sticking through my leg-
Hey, an agate.
Damnit.
Janet.
She's gotta call back.
She's got to.
Maybe if we stare at
the phone really hard.
(laughs)
What are you guys doing?
Let's see you swim with
this on your leg, baby.
It would be less incriminating
if they threw her in the river.
Huh, huh?
Oh, oh.
Not the Hamilton Beach!
It's the cover of
the Nirvana album.
(gasping)
Oh, it's a fiendish plot
to ruin her hair with chlorine.
Couldn't we have thrown her
in the deep end, boss?
The common sophomore
blends easily into
its surroundings.
Hot shrub action.
♪ Running, running,
running, running
♪ She's running,
♪ And running and running and
Thank you.
♪ Running, she's
really, really running
♪ She's running, she's running
Thank you, yes.
♪ And running
Wow, she's easily discouraged.
(laughs)
You'e a fumbling fool.
But you look good in a Speedo.
Fear of death is
the quickest way.
Just watch and learn.
It's a wet teacher
contest (laughs)
♪ Running and running,
now she's running
♪ And look, she's
running down the hill
♪ And she's running and
running and running
(sighs) Can I have
permission to hit him?
♪ And running and running
♪ And she's really,
really running
Mom, can you pick me up?
I'm done with play practice.
(phone rings)
Yes.
I got it.
Stay out of sight
'til we get there.
We're on our way.
Arthur Godfrey's in trouble!
(laughs)
(gasping)
They're drowning Cousin It.
Oh, Miss.
Miss, this is really
getting quite silly.
And I'm running out of patience.
Really?
I'm having a good time!
Just give us the
names of the others!
I'm the...
I did it myself.
I did it all myself.
Teacher has it in for me, man.
Stop, stop!
You're driving
over my hopscotch!
♪ Running and running
Up the hill.
Did you see any guards?
Two at the gate.
Let's get 'em.
Come on, Keiko.
Sports bar waitresses
to the rescue!
Having the headquarters
on Pike's Peak
is kind of a pain.
(whispering)
You know, a lot of people say
I look like Fred Willard.
Don't touch my
Kiana, it'll snag.
If you hunch over,
people can't see you.
In study hall there's
this really cute guy.
We work well together, Vito.
Hey, psst.
(groans)
(grunts)
Owie, ouch, ouch,
owie, ow, ow, ouch.
Don't watch the
jiggling, honey.
Killing, and
killing, and dying.
All right, Trish,
you wait here.
I, I, I, uh, I
forgot how to talk.
Oh darn.
(theme music)
This is kind of a light
motif of this movie.
Park far away and run to
the scene of the caper.
Can't get this helmet on.
Oh God, it's my Aunt Thelma.
Hold it!
Hyack!
That's the pool
cleaning guy, oh.
(gunfire)
(groans)
My rascal bark chow-chow
the drat drilled his knickers.
Baby!
I will want you!
(dog barking)
Hyah!
He didn't count on her
having a way with pets.
(whimpering)
Freeze, sweetheart!
(gunfire)
Eat lead, Freddy Prinz!
(mumbles)
(gunfire)
I just remembered, Dr.
Quinn, Medicine Woman is on.
And Mark Spitz wins
another gold medal
in the jean jacket freestyle.
Ya!
Oh, now she's having a
Sherman Oaks flashback.
(muttering)
I hurt my pants!
(bike roaring)
Would you quit following me?
(gunfire)
Jim Henson!
Hi, ho!
Oh!
Peter's parties are nuts, man.
I regret nothing!
Greg Louganis
goes motorcycling!
(intense music)
Hell's Angels on wheels,
starring Esther Williams.
What's with the Philip Glass?
Aw, what a touching
underwater love scene.
Yeah, yeah I can see
why she needed the
motorcycle to do this.
Say, neo-Gothic, really nice.
(gunfire)
What do you do?
Shoot the hostage.
(whimpering)
Lady Blue.
Susan, what are you doing?
Easy, it's all right now.
You're all right.
Take it easy.
Are you all right?
You just bought
a one-way ticket
to the (gunfire) ooh!
(grunts)
The sensibly dressed commando.
Is everybody all right?
Is everyone okay?
Here, let me help you.
Would you like
a glass of water?
Keiko, are you all right?
Yeah, yeah I'm all right.
Kelsey Grammar was
supposed to meet me here.
(singing)
♪ French stuff, French stuff
Ah, that booze
really refreshed me.
Plink, plink, plink, plink.
Plink, plink,
plink, plink, plink.
Ah, switching strategies.
He's going into the wine cellar.
Cheryl Ladd is
woefully miscast
in the Will Mogedal story.
(murmuring)
All right, paper boy,
if you miss the porch
one more time...
Okay, here's the plan.
Everyone get home and
condition, right now.
(yelp)
All over, ladies.
Just relax and don't
make any sudden moves.
Guess what, Randy kissed me!
(gunfire)
(screams)
Drop it, mister!
I'll take that.
Would this be a bad
time to ask you out?
You guys go check on Trish.
I'll tell you what,
I'll call Miller.
He'll take care of everything.
Hold it!
Who's got a corkscrew?
One minute.
Let's tie him up with this.
Now the bad guys
are constantly
being rewarded in this film.
Get in there.
He's not going anywhere.
Yes he is, you
locked him outside.
(dog barking)
Oh no, he saw City Slickers 2.
(mumbles)
They're overcome
with mild concern.
You, drop your guns,
get down here.
Oh, they got a hot dog stand
right there by the pool.
All right, you girls
did a pretty good job.
(imitates slurred speech)
But you didn't
quite have the control
you thought you had.
Control.
I learned a long time ago
to eliminate any
possible (gunfire)
(gasping)
(grunting)
I may have been shot.
(gasps)
Shoot, now I'm sober.
By this time my lungs
were aching from booze.
You wanna skim
the Peter Lawford off your pool.
Trish!
You better go
study for your test!
Trish, are you all right?
Did I do all right?
Am I one of the seven now?
Yes, little Trish,
you're one of us.
Hang on.
Don't worry, Hewitt can't
kill one of the seven.
She is so
delusional right now.
(dramatic music)
As Lucretia MacEvil.
As thank you,
Mr. Eddie's father.
As the plain,
unremarkable one.
Died in Vietnam.
As Lorraine Newman.
As Greg Allman.
As J. Edgar Hoover.
(disco music)
Okay baby, let's get
funky now, '70s style.
Now Mike, you gotta tell me,
what caused the '70s?
What do you mean, David?
I mean, this whole '70s,
who came up with it?
Uh, the '70s,
well, I think they were
developed by Robert Steakwood.
Ah.
Actually, I think the
'70s were made up
by either England Dan or John
Portcoli, I'm not sure which.
I think they both
came up with it
at the same time, thus,
the legend was born.
Look, Cody Palance,
he's Jack Donaldson's
tough, street-smart,
wise-cracking,
crime-fighting son.
(singing)
Yeah.
Now isn't Can't Stop the Music
with the Village People tied
up with the '70s somehow?
Yes, but don't diminish
the importance of Nancy Walker.
No, I didn't mean
to imply that--
Well whenever anyone mentions
Can't Stop the Music they
forget about Nancy Walker,
it's not right.
Jeez, all I was saying--
It just gets me
mad, that's all.
Woah, woah, ,woah.
Hey, I know who was
important during the '70s,
the Eagles.
You're damn right
they were important.
They almost
single-handedly sustained
the economy of Columbia.
For some reason when
I think of the '70s
I think of Melanie.
I do too, you know,
Brand New Key,
Lay Down Lay Down,
candles at her concerts,
that kind of thing?
No, no, no I was gonna
say Melanie Chartoff.
Friday spoke to a
whole generation, man.
When you talk about the
'70s, you can't forget
the scandal that
rocked the decade.
You know what I'm
talking about, right?
Of course, you
mean when Ed Vigoda
left Barney Miller to
start on Phish, right?
I never got over that.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
I was thinking of
Watergate, Watergate.
Well what the hell
did Ed Vigoda
have to do with Watergate?
Nothing.
Then why are you
dragging him into it?
You said I could, would, oh.
You two.
(chuckles)
Hey, remember when everybody
had this poster here?
Except that there
was only one of them
and it was Farrah Fawcett?
Remember that?
Yeah.
(imitating laser noises)
All breasts, whether
actual or created
are based on authenticated fact.
Hey, where was Bruce
Jenner in this movie?
He's the one on the left.
(singing)
(mechanical whirring)
Mike, there were
a whole lot of
shameful performances
in today's movie.
Why, even your run-of-the-
mill palooka like Crow here
can tell you that much.
He's right, I could.
But now, thanks to my
fantastic new invention,
mankind are able
to measure exactly
how shameful it was.
What this little thing?
The Shame-o-Meter?
Sham-om-eter, Mike.
Hey Shamometer bup
deep buh dee deep.
How charming.
Shut up, Crow.
Mike, shame emits tiny
waves best measured in
nits of Lawfords, kilo-Lawfords,
mega-Lawfords and so on.
Cambot, if you please.
Well, howdy girls, shall
I gasoline her up for you?
See there?
We're in mega-Lawford range.
I'd say that's pretty shameful.
Let's try something else.
Cambot.
I am Commander Lindsay Mark,
commander of the
(machine whirring)
Jim Backus on the machine
registers well into
the giga-Lawford
range, so in order to
get an accurate reading,
I'm going to have to
retrofit this baby--
No, no, that's quite
all right, Servo.
You know though, you,
young man have performed
a valuable service here today.
(alarms ringing)
Huh?
What the?
Oh my God, there's an
unidentifed source,
this could be well
into the Google shame!
Mike, it was pointless
and silly of us
to dress as '70s
relief pitchers,
and to rectify the situation
we've decided to
dress as Bobby Riggs
and Billy Jean King.
Because Mike, we pride ourselves
on being topical and current.
Hey you lousy
woman, rectify this.
(glass shattering)
(synthesizer music)
(disco music)